Guide to the Johan Kugelberg hip hop collection, circa 1975-1985, 2008.
Kugelberg, Johan hip hop collection,
- Series I. Sound Recordings (1-24)
  - CDs - CD 360-398 (Box 20)
    - Harlem World, 1981 Performed by: AJ, Busy Bee, Master Don, Death Committee, Pebbley, Gangsta Gee, K.C., Cold Crush 4, and L.A. Sunshine, 1981; CD-364 (Box 20)
    - Bronx, 1980-1982 Performed by: Spoonie G., Wanda Dee, Doug E. Fresh, the Fantastic 5, the Force MC's, Busy Bee, Kool DJ AJ, and Stetsasonic, 1982; CD-365 (Box 20)
    - T connection Part 2 Performed by: L Brothers and Zulu Nation, 1978; CD-366 (Box 20)
    - St Marks Park Bk Part 1 Performed by: Grandmaster Flowers, 1979; CD-367 (disc 1) (Box 20)
    - St Marks Park Bk Part 2 Performed by: Grandmaster Flowers, 1979; CD-368 (disc 2) (Box 20)
    - Audubon & Jackson projects Performed by: Grandmaster Flash and the Furious 4, ca. 1985; CD-369 (Box 20)
    - Connecticut, 1980 Performed by: DD Lady Love, Infinity Machine, Disco Kid, Divine, DJ Easy Lee, the Treacherous 3, and Spoonie Gee, 1980; CD-370 (Box 20)
    - 30th annual Zulu anniversary: Hip-hop history month, November Performed by: Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Funky 4 + 1 More, and others, 2003; CD-371 (Box 20)
    - Zulu beats / P Brothers Performed by: P Brothers, ca. 1975; CD-372 (Box 20)
    - Savoy manor Performed by: Cold Crush Brothers and the Fantastic Five, 1982; CD-373 (Box 20)
    - T connection Performed by: Funky 4 plus 1, ca. 1985; CD-374 (Box 20)
    - Battle of the DJ's Performed by: DJ's Charlie Chase, Jazzy Jay, DJ Whiz Kid, the Cold Crush Brothers, and others, 1981; CD-375 (Box 20)
    - Battle of the century / Kool Moe Dee vs Chiefrocker Busy Bee Performed by: Kool Moe Dee and Busy Bee, ca. 1985; CD-376 (Box 20)
    - DJ breakout & Baron Performed by: Funky 4 plus 1, 1980; CD-377 (Box 20)
    - T connection Part 2 Performed by: Deb D, 1978; CD-378 (Box 20)
      Publisher: Bronx River
    - Hip hop Mp3s Performed by: Various performers, ca. 2000; CD-379 (disc 1) (Box 20)
    - Hip hop Mp3s Performed by: Various performers, ca. 2000; CD-380 (disc 2) (Box 20)
    - Cold Crush Brothers live: at 1) Harlem World, 1981; 2) Hoe Ave Boys Club, 1981 Performed by: Cold Crush Brothers, 1981; CD-381 (Box 20)
    - Super showdown: Coldcrush vs Fantastic, Fri, July 3, 1981 Performed by: Cold Crush and the Fantastic Five, 1981; CD-382 (Box 20)
    - It had to happen: Charley Chase, Toney Tone, Theodore, Coldcrush vs Fantastic, 1,00000 cash, winner takes all; Starski, HarlemWorldCrew, live in concert at Harlem World Performed by: Charley Chase, Tony Tone, Theodore, Cold Crush, the Fantastic Five, Lovebug Starski, and Harlem World, ca. 1985; CD-383 (Box 20)
    - Coldcrush; Fearless 4 Performed by: Cold Crush and the Fearless Four, ca. 1985; CD-384 (Box 20)
    - Battle of the century: live from Harlem World Entertainment Complex, Dec 30th, 1980 / featuring Kool Moe Dee vs Busy Bee Performed by: Kool Moe Dee and Busy Bee, 1981; CD-385 (Box 20)
    - Queens Armory Performed by: [Unknown], ca. 1985; CD-386 (Box 20)
    - Harlem World anniversary Performed by: Various performers, 1983; CD-387 (Box 20)
    - Coldcrush, Whiz Kid Performed by: Cold Crush and Whiz Kid, ca. 1985; CD-388 (Box 20)
    - Force MCs, Dr. Rock, Stevie-D, Mercury, Jesse-D, vs Charlie Chase, Tony Tone, GM Caz, JDL, Easy AD, KG, the Coldcrush Brothers Performed by: Force MC's, Dr. Rock, Stevie D., Mercury, Jesse D., Charlie Chase, Tony Tone, Grandmaster Caz, J.D.L., Easy AD, KG and the Cold Crush Brothers, ca. 1985; CD-389 (Box 20)
    - Harlem World, 1983 / Master Don, the Master Don Committee Performed by: Masterdon Committee, 1983; CD-390 (Box 20)
    - S.O.B.'s, '93: Coldcrush live Performed by: Cold Crush, 1993; CD-391 (Box 20)
    - Hip hop essentials, 1979-1991 Volume five Performed by: Various performers, 2006; CD-392 (Box 20)
      Publisher: Tommy Boy Entertainment
      Track listing: That's the joint / Funky Four + 1 -- Freedom / Grandmaster Flash & The Furious Five -- Bring the noize / Public Enemy -- It takes two / Rob Base & DJ E-Z Rock -- Wild wild west / Kool Moe Dee -- Fat boys / The Fat Boys -- Making cash money / Busy Bee -- Ring ring ring (Ha ha hey) / De La Soul -- Jimbrowski / Jungle Brothers -- Ladies first / Queen Latifah/Monie Love -- Hey dj / World Famous Supreme Team -- Money (Dollar bill y'all) / Jimmy Spicer.
    - Hip hop essentials, 1979-1991 Volume two Performed by: Various performers, 2005; CD-393 (Box 20)
      Track listing: Rebel without a pause / Public Enemy -- Last night / Kid n Play -- Nobody beats the Biz / Biz Markie -- Paper thin / MC Lyte -- Goin' back to Cali / LL Cool J -- Plug Tunin' / De La Sol -- Bust a move / Young MC -- Looking at the front door / Main Source -- Cinderfella / Dana Dane -- Be a father to your child / Ed O G & the Bulldogs -- Just Buggin' / Whistle -- F**k Compton / Tim Dog.
    - Hip hop essentials, 1979-1991 Volume four Performed by: Various performers, 2005; CD-394 (Box 20)
      Track listing: White lines / Grand Master Flash & Furious 5 -- Roxanne Roxanne / UTFO -- Don't believe the hype / Public Enemy -- Ego trippin' / Ultramagnetic MCs -- Raw / Big Daddy Kane -- Mentirosa / Mellow Man Ace -- Around the way girl / LL Cool J -- It's yours / T-la Rock -- Sucker MCs / Run-DMC -- 8 million stories / Kurtis Blow -- Go see the doctor / Kool Moe Dee -- Me so horny / 2 Live Crew.
    - Hip hop essentials, 1979-1991 Volume three Performed by: Various performers, 2005; CD-395 (Box 20)
      Track listing: Microphone fiend / Eric B & Rakim -- Bonita applebaum / A Tribe Called Quest -- Parents just don't understand / Jazzy Jeff & Fresh Prince -- Funky cold medina / Tone Loc -- Gold digger / EPMD -- F**k the police / N.W.A. -- The 900 number / 45 King -- Bitch betta have my money / AMG -- This cut's got flavor / Latee -- Ain't no half-steppin' / Big Daddy Kane -- Humpty dance / Digital Underground -- Pee Wee's dance / Joeski Love.
    - Greatest beats, the first fifteen years 1981-1996 Volume 4 Performed by: Various performers, 1998; CD-396 (Box 20)
      Track listing: Gangsta bitch (Apache) (4:47) -- Hip hop hooray (Naughty by Nature) (4:25) -- Potholes in my lawn: (12" version) (De La Soul) (3:48) -- Pack jam (look out for the OVC): (7" version) (Jonzun Crew) (4:28) --Louder than love (TKA) (4:31) -- Running: (12" version) (Information Society) (7:42) -- Supermodel (you better work) (RuPaul) (3:45) -- Kiss you back (Digital Underground) (6:11) -- Rock the house (you'll never be) (Pressure Drop) (4:23) -- Talkin' all that jazz (Stetsasonic) (4:49) -- Non stop (Sweet Trio) (5:50) -- Play that beat Mr. DJ (G.L.O.B.E. + Whiz Kid) (4:00) -- Tender love (Force MD's) (3:55) --Gangsta's paradise (Coolio) (3:48).
    - Drew's famous Caribbean party music Performed by: Various performers, 1990; CD-397 (Box 20)
      Publisher: Turn Up the Music
      Track listing: Caribbean queen -- Get down on it -- Bamboleo -- Island girl -- Pull up to the bumper -- Turn the beat around -- Buffalo soldier -- Eye of the tiger -- Rapper's delight -- Brick house -- Rock you like a hurricane -- Love train -- Night fever -- What I like about you -- Boogie nights -- Gotta get back to the islands.
    - Steinski's burning out of control: the Sugarhill mix Performed by: Various performers, 2003; CD-398 (Box 20)
      Publisher: Sanctuary Records
      Track listing: Freestyle (Grandmaster Melle Mel & The Furious Five) -- Livin' in the fast lane (Sugar Hill Gang) -- Spoonie's back (Spoonie G.) -- Makin' cash money (Busy Bee) -- Fi-ya up that funk (Sequence) -- Yes we can-can (interlude) (Treacherous 3) -- Do you know what time it is? (Kool Moe Dee) -- Why can't people be colours too? (interlude) (Whatnauts) -- Busy Bee's groove (Busy Bee) -- Feel the heartbeat (Treacherous 3) -- Monster jam (Sequence (featuring Spoonie G.)) -- It's good to be the queen (Sylvia) -- That's the joint; Joint remix (Funky 4 + 1 More) -- Freedom (Grandmaster Flash & The Furious 5) -- Disco dream (Mean machine) -- We got the funk (interlude) (Positive force) -- Breakdance electric boogie (West St. Mob) -- Grandmaster Flash on the wheels of steel (Grandmaster Flash) -- Let's dance (West St. Mob) -- Superrappin'; Scorpio (Grandmaster Flash & The Furious 5) -- I can't stop (West St. Mob) -- Outro.
  - CDs - CD 399-414, includes duplicates (Box 21)
    - Greatest beats, the first fifteen years 1981-1996 Volume 1 Performed by: Various performers, 1998; CD-399 (Box 21)
      Track listing: Planet rock (Afrika Bambaataa + Soul Sonic Force) (3:37) -- Everything's gonna be all right (Naughty by Nature) (3:02) -- Doowutchyalike (Digital Underground) (4:45) -- Plug tunin' (are you ready for this): (12" version) (De La Soul) (3:44) -- Can't you see (Total, featuring the Notorious B.I.G.) (4:53) -- Move it like this (K7) (4:23) -- Gordy's groove (Choice MCs, featuring Fresh Gordon) (4:13) -- Play at your own risk: (12" version) (Planet Patrol) (7:50) -- Sally (Stetsasonic) (4:32) -- Ladies first (Queen Latifah, featuring Monie Love) (3:54) -- Renegades of funk: (12" version) (Africa Bambaataa + Soul Sonic Force) (6:44) -- Lean on me (Club Nouveau) (5:51) -- Tears (Force M.D.'s) (4:20) -- Unity (Afrika Bambaataa + the Godfather of Soul James Brown) (3:25).
    - Nyuorican poets cafe / DJ Disco Wiz Performed by: DJ Disco Wiz, 2000; CD-400 (Box 21)
      Publisher: DJ Disco Wiz
    - Third unheard: Connecticut Hip Hop 1979-1983 Performed by: Various performers, 2004; CD-401 (Box 21)
      Track listing: Rappin' with Mr. Magic -- Get up (and go to school) -- Potential 1980 -- Party people (remix) -- Million dollar legs (RAP) -- 2001 kazoo's -- Be-bop convention theme -- Shake your boody -- Fill the be-bop -- Earth break -- Ventriloquist rap -- I just wanna dance -- Showdown rehearsal LIVE!
    - Third unheard: Connecticut Hip Hop 1979-1983 Performed by: Various performers, 2004; CD-401 c.2 (Box 21)
    - Body stance: original old skool party rockers Performed by: Various performers, 2002; CD-402 (Box 21)
      Track listing: Marley Marl scratch (Marley Marl) -- Listen to the man (Kev E Kev; Freddy Fresh cut-up) -- B boy style (Lil' Jazzy Jay & Cool Supreme) -- Listen to the man (Kev E Kev; Freddy Fresh beats) -- Wack rap scratch (Wackies Disco Band; Freddy Fresh cut-up) -- TSO (Master Jay & Michael Dee) -- Techno scratch (Knights of the Turntable) -- Ain't no half steppin' (promo mix) (Big Daddy Kane) -- Advance (Scott La Rock & The Celebrity Three) -- Scoopy rap (Scoopy; Freddy Fresh beats) -- Coolin' on the ave (Freddy B & The Mighty Mic Masters feat. Captain Gee Whiz) -- Strong island (JVC Force) -- Taking the waterfront by force (Ian Darby) -- Monster rock (Something Anything; Freddy Fresh beats) -- Party scene (Russell Brothers) -- Standing on the top (Super 3) -- Bounce, rock, skateroll (Trickeration) -- B boy breakdown (dub) (Hi Fidelity 3; Freddy Fresh beats) -- We come to rock (Imperial Brothers; Freddy Fresh mix) -- Def jam (Jazzy Jay) -- Juice Crew dis (Cool C) -- Triple threat (Z3MCs) -- Get off my tip (Masterdon Committee) -- Monster rock (Something Anything) -- Human beat box (Disco Three) -- Strong island (blue mix) (JVC Force) -- Party rap (Bobby Deemo).
    - Death mix: the best of Paul Winley Records Performed by: Various performers, 2001; CD-403 (Box 21)
      Publisher: LandSpeed Records
      Track listing: Zulu nation throwdown (Afrika Bambaata & The Cosmic Force) -- Zulu nation throwdown, pt. 2 (Afrika Bambaata & The Soulsonic Force) -- Death mix, pt. 1 (live); Death mix, pt. 2 (live) (Afrika Bambaata) -- Smokin cheeba cheeba (Harlem Underground Band) -- Watch dog (Ann Winley) -- Rhymin & rappin (Paulette & Tanya "Sweet Tee" Winley) -- Vicious rap (Tanya "Sweet Tee" Winley) -- Finger in it (The Mighty Tomcats) -- Ain't no sunshine (Harlem Underground Band) -- Back up push baby (Ann Winley & Harlem Underground Band).
    - Vinyl exams Performed by: Various performers, 2000; CD-404 (Box 21)
      Publisher: Sony Music
      Track listing: P.S.K.: what does it mean / Schoolly D -- WCMI intro -- Ego-trippin' (MC Ultra) / Ultramagnetic MC's -- Rockin' it / Fearless Four -- Body rock / Treacherous Three -- One nation -- Going way back / Just-Ice -- Bam bam bam -- Bring the beat back / Steady B -- Girls I got em locked / Super Lover Cee & Casanova Rud -- Prince -- Stick em / Fat Boys -- Def fresh crew / Roxanne Shante and Biz Markie -- It's my beat / Sweet Tee & Jazzy Joyce -- Sons of cypher -- Peter Piper / Run-D.M.C. -- My 3 kings -- Fresh / Fresh 3 MC's.
    - Big Apple rappin' Performed by: Various performers, 2006; CD-405 (disc 1) (Box 21)
      Track listing: Spoonin' rap (Spoonin [i.e. Spoonie] Gee) -- Sure shot (Xanadu) -- How we gonna make the Black nation rise? (Brother "D", with Collective Effort) -- Rapping dub style (General Echo) -- Catch the beat (T-Ski Valley) -- Dancing heart (Universal 2) -- Funk box party (The Masterdon Committee) -- Weekend (Cold Crush Brothers) -- Big Apple rappin' (Spyder D) -- D.J. style (Mr. Q) -- Fly Guys rap (The Fly Guys) -- Get the party jumpin' (Solo Sound) -- Rock the beat (Jamaica Girls) -- When you're standing on top (Super 3) -- Are you ready? (T.J. Swann, Peewee Mel, Barry B) -- The ultimate rap (Nice & Nasty 3).
    - Big Apple rappin' Performed by: Various performers, 2006; CD-406 (disc 2) (Box 21)
    - Greatest beats, the first fifteen years 1981-1996 Volume 3 Performed by: Various performers, 1998; CD-407 (Box 21)
      Track listing: O.P.P. (Naughty by Nature) (4:30) -- Go Stetsa I: (12" remix) (Stetsasonic) (7:32) -- Me, myself and I (De La Soul) (3:40) -- Shamrocks and shenanigans (boom shalock lock boom): (Butch Vig remix) (House of Pain) (3:56) -- Looking for the perfect beat: (12" version) (Afrika Bambaataa + Soul Sonic Force) (4:31) -- What's on your mind: (pure energy mix) (Information Society) (4:35) -- Maria: (12" vocal) (TKA) (6:56) -- People hold on (Coldcut, featuring Lisa Stansfield) (3:56) --Fantastic voyage: (timber mix) (Coolio) (5:34) -- Why you treat me so bad (Club Nouveau) (5:07) -- Same song (Digital Underground) (3:58) -- Break the grip of shame (Paris) (3:34) -- Latifah's had it up to here (Queen Latifah) (4:28) -- Here I go again (Force M.D.'s) (6:26).
    - Greatest beats, the first fifteen years 1981-1996 Volume 2 Performed by: Various performers, 1998; CD-408 (Box 21)
      Track listing: Jump around (House of Pain) (3:38) -- Uptown anthem (Naughty by Nature) (3:03) -- Jealousy (Club Nouveau) (4:45) -- Cheap thrills: (12" version) (Planet Patrol) (6:47) -- Come baby come (K7) (4:07) -- 1, 2, 3, 4 (sumpin' new): (timber mix) (Coolio) (3:22) --Come into my house (Queen Latifah) (4:18) -- Buddy: (12" remix) (De La Soul featuring A Tribe Called Quest ... [et al.]) (7:15) -- Jazzy sensation: (12" remix) (Afrika Bambaataa + The Jazzy 5) (5:43) -- Feel me flow (Naughty by Nature) (3:33) -- The humpty dance (Digital Underground) (6:30) -- Let me love you (Force MD's) (3:43) -- Pacific (808 State) (4:20) -- Ring ring ring (ha ha hey) (De La Soul) (3:25).
    - Super rap: original rap & hip hop from Harlem's P & P Records Performed by: Various performers, 2002; CD-409 (Box 21)
    - Disco juice: the funky disco sound of Harlem's P & P Records Performed by: Various performers, 2000; CD-410 (Box 21)
      Publisher: Counterpoint Records
      Track listing: Johnson jumpin' (Johnson Products) -- African rock (Licky) -- Dance freak (Chain Reaction) -- Got to have your love (Clyde Alexander) -- Ain't it time (Queen Yahna) -- Hooked on your line (L.J. Williams) -- Feel the spirit (Foster Johnson) -- N.Y. applejack (Scott Davis) -- Out of work (Jesse Gould) -- Get down boy (Paper Doll) -- Disco juice (re-edit); Flying high; Patti Duke (Cloud One).
    - Disco juice Volume 2, soul, disco & rap from Harlem's P & P Records Performed by: Various performers, 2002; CD-411 (Box 21)
      Track listing: Magic carpet (Hi Fidelity) -- The groove I'm in (Florence Miller) -- 25 hours (Lanier) -- Death rap (Margo's Kool Out Crew) -- Roller rink funk (Shift) -- Willie rap (Willie Wood & Willie Wood Crew) -- Super-Jay love theme (Super-Jay) -- I did it again (Jesse Henderson) -- The guardian angel is watching over us (Golden Flamingo Orch. featuring Margo Williams) -- Game of life (Lavaba & E. Mallison) -- Dust to dust (Cloud One).
    - Hip hop roots: it's breakbeat era: the hits that started it all Performed by: Various performers, 2005; CD-412 (Box 21)
      Track listing: It's just begun (the Jimmy Castor Bunch) -- The big beat (Billy Squier) -- Think (about it) (Lyn Collins feat. the JB's) -- Take me to the Mardi Gras (Bob James) -- Fame (David Bowie) -- Happy music (the Blackbyrds) -- Express yourself (Charles Wright & the Watts 103rd Street Rhythmn [sic] Band) -- Bra (Cymande) -- Mary, Mary (the Monkees) -- Let a woman be a woman (let a man be a man) (Dyke & the Blazers) -- Give it up or turnit a loose (James Brown) -- UFO (ESG).
    - Fast rap / Edan the DJ Performed by: Various performers, 2001; CD-413 (Box 21)
      Publisher: Edan the DJ
      Track listing: Raw (Big Daddy Kane & Kool Rap) -- Freestyle (Melle Mel) -- Prisoners of war (Organized Konfusion) -- Welcome to the terrordome (inst.) -- Axe-maniac (Unique) -- Mission accomplished (Bizzie Boyz) -- Something for the bassline -- Back to back rhyming (Lord Finesse & A.G.) -- The creator (Pete Rock & C.L. Smooth) -- Warm it up, Kane (Big Daddy Kane) -- At the drop of a dime (inst.) -- Small time hustler; Black & proud (Dismasters) -- Stop the world (Black, Rock & Ron) -- Reflection of perfection (MC Jewel) -- He got so much soul (Main Source) -- Now ya know (Freshco & Miz) -- Kool is back (Kool G Rap & DJ Polo) -- Lung collapsing lyrics (Percee P & Ekim) -- Chorus line (Ultramagnetic MCs) -- Real solo please stand up (K-Solo) -- Rampage (remix) (EPMD & LL Cool J) -- Jokes on you Jack (inst.) -- Strobelite honey (remix) (Black Sheep) -- It's that simple (Jaz & Jay Zee) -- I'm the peacemaker (Sir Ibu of Divine Force) -- Know the ledge (Eric B & Rakim) -- Lo-fi bonus: Percee P vs. Lord Finesse: Patterson Projects battle 1989.
    - Tommy Boy's greatest beats: the remixes Performed by: Various performers, 1998; CD-414 (Box 21)
      Track listing: Jump around (House of Pain) (2:53) -- Wrath of my madness (Queen Latifah) (4:46) -- Talkin' all that jazz (Stetsasonic) (10:01) -- Me, myself and I (De la Soul) (4:01) -- Looking for the perfect beat (Afrika Bambaataa + Soul Sonic Force) (8:20) -- Pack jam (Look out for the OVC) (Jonzun Crew) (6:50) -- Play at your own risk (Planet Patrol) (4:03) -- Planet rock (Afrika Bambaataa + Soul Sonic Force) (6:17) -- Tender love (Force M.D.'s) (5:20).
  - Expansion space (Box 22-24)
  - CDs - CD 1470-1510, Prints created by Cornell Library’s digital reproduction lab in 2014 for Joe Conzo’s exhibition at the Rock and Roll Hall of fame (Box 46-47)
    - Live performance at Patterson, N.J. Performed by: The Fearless 4, Master Don and the Death Committee at Patterson, N.J., CC4 at Harlem World, n.d.; CD-1470 (Box 46)
    - Live performance at Cadet Headquarters Performed by: Cold Crush 4, T. Ski Valley, CC4, Harlem World, n.d.; CD-1471 (Box 46)
    - Live performance Performed by: Grand Master Flash and Grand Wizard Theodore, The L Bros, n.d.; CD-1472 (Box 46)
    - Live performance Performed by: Grand Master Flash, Furious 5 (Flash on beat box), n.d.; CD-1473 (Box 46)
    - Treacherous Three Anniversary Performed by: Cold Crush Brothers, Fearless Four, n.d.; CD-1474 (Box 46)
    - Live performance Performed by: Grand Wizard Theodore, The Original L Brothers, featuring D.J.'s Mean Gene and Cordio, 1977; CD-1475 (Box 46)
    - Mr. Hyde, Mr. Bond Performed by: DJ Ronnie Green at the Foster Center, 1977; CD-1476 (Box 46)
    - Live performance at the T-Connection Performed by: Grand Wizard Theodore, Amazing Mean Gene, DJ Claudio, Busy Bee, Starsky, Robbie Rob (Master Rob), Kevie Kev (Water Bed), The Original L Bros, 1978; CD-1477 (Box 46)
    - Live performance at the T-Connection Performed by: L Bros, Zulu Nation, L Bros vs. The Herculoids, 1978; CD-1478 (Box 46)
    - Live performance at the T-Connection Performed by: Grand Master Flash, The Furious 5, 1979; CD-1479 (Box 46)
    - Live performance at the T-Connection Performed by: Melle Mel, Mr. Ness, Cowboy, Rahiem, Grand Master Flash - first time on beat box, 1979; CD-1480 (Box 46)
    - Live performance Performed by: Grand Master Flash and The Furious 5, 1979; CD-1481 (Box 46)
    - Live performance at the T-Connection Performed by: DJ Sinbad, Kool Kyle, Grand Master Flash, 1979; CD-1482 (Box 46)
    - Live performance at the T-Connection Performed by: DJ Breakout, DJ Barren, Lil Rodney C, KK Rockwell, Sha Rock, Keith Keith, Jazzy Jaff, Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde - Ronnie Green, 1979; CD-1483 (Box 46)
    - Live performance at Celebrity Club Performed by: Grand Master Flash, Melle Mel, Eman, Grand Wizard Theodore, Kevie Kev, Ruby Dee, Master Rob, L Bros, Mc Smiley, Spoonie G, LA Sunshine, Treacherous 3, Busy Bee, Tiny, Kool Moe Dee, Special K, 1980; CD-1484 (Box 46)
    - Live performance at the T-Connection Performed by: Grand Master Flash and the Furious 5, 1980; CD-1485 (Box 46)
    - Live performance at the T-Connection Performed by: Grand Wizard Theodore, Kevie Kev, Master Rob, Whipper Whip, Dotta Rock, MC Rubie Dee, DJ Clark Kent, Fantastic 5, 1980; CD-1486 (Box 46)
    - Live performance at the T-Connection Performed by: Grand Master Flash and the Furious 5, 1980; CD-1487 (Box 46)
    - Live performance Performed by: Zulu Nation and The L Brothers, 1980; CD-1488 (Box 46)
    - Live performance Performed by: none listed, 1980; CD-1489 (Box 46)
    - Live performance at Ecstasy Garage Performed by: Cold Crush Bros, 1980; CD-1490 (Box 46)
    - Live performance Performed by: Funky 4 Plus One More, 1980; CD-1491 (Box 46)
    - Live performance at St. Andrews H.S. Performed by: DJ Holiday, Master Ice, Master Bee, Master Dee, Mr. Freeze, 1981; CD-1492 (Box 46)
    - Live performance (Disk 1) Performed by: DJ Charlie Chase, The Cold Crush 4, Grand Master Caz, JDL, Easy AD, All Mighty KG, Grand Wizard Theodore and Fantastic 5, Master Rob, Kevie Kev, Whipper Whip, Dotta Rock, Ruby-Dee, n.d.; CD-1493 (Box 46)
    - Cold Crush vs. Fantastics, Harlem World (Disk 2) Performed by: DJ Charlie Chase, The Cold Crush 4, Grand Master Caz, JDL, Easy AD, All Mighty KG, Grand Wizard Theodore and Fantastic 5, Master Rob, Kevie Kev, Whipper Whip, Dotta Rock, Ruby-Dee, 1981; CD-1494 (Box 46)
    - Harlem World, MC Contest Performed by:T-Ski Vally, Spoony G, Busy Bee, Dr. Rock, Force Mc's, Grand Wizard Theodore, Fantastics, Charlie Chase, Cold Crush 4, 1981; CD-1495 (Box 46)
    - Live performance at Audubon Performed by: DJ AJ, Grand Wizard Theodore, Kevie Kev, Busy Bee, 1981; CD-1496 (Box 46)
    - Live performance at Harlem World Performed by:Cold Crush Bros vs. Fantastic 5, 1981; CD-1497 (Box 46)
    - X-Mas Convention Performed by: Busy Bee vs Kool Moe Dee, 1981; CD-1498 (Box 47)
    - Live performance Printing H.S. (Disk 1) Performed by: Force MC's, Busy Bee, CC4, JS, 1981; CD-1499 (Box 47)
    - Live performance Printing H.S. (Disk)2 Performed by: Force Mc's, Busy Bee, CC4, JS, 1981; CD-1500 (Box 47)
    - Live performance at the T-Connection Performed by: Grand Master Flash, Fantastic 5, Bam, Jazzys MC's, 1981; CD-1501 (Box 47)
    - Kool Moe Dee vs Busy Bee, Harlem World Performed by: Force MC's, DJ Tystick, Jhonny Wild, DJ AJ and Busy Bee, DJ Easy Lee, LA Sunshine, Kool Moe Dee, Cold Crush Bros, 1981; CD-1502 (Box 47)
    - Live performance at Savo's Manor Night Club Performed by: Fantastic 5, Cold Crush Bros, 1982; CD-1503 (Box 47)
    - Live performance at Skating Palace Performed by: Kurtis Blow, Cold Crush Bros, 1982; CD-1504 (Box 47)